http://www.bobbycogdell.com/home/privacy_policy

Cogdell Insurance Agency111 North Main StreetLexington, TN 38351ph: 731-968-4300fax: 731-968-4001bobbycogdell@charter.netHOMEPrivacy Policy
WILMA COGDELL COGDELL SOLAR ALDERMAN COGDELL SCHOLARSHIPSThe Cogdell Family Memorial Scholarship Fund The Cogdell Insurance Agency Scholarship The Frank & Wilma Cogdell Memorial Scholarship Fund The John Henry Cogdell Scholarship
NEW COGDELL HOMEHome Tour Video
STEWART HOMEStewart Home Photos
COGDELL WATERFALL COGDELL SUNFLOWERSSunflower Farm Photos
COGDELL HISTORY BUFF COGDELL FAMILY COGDELL ANCESTORS COGDELL CEMETERYCogdell Cemetery Photos
COGDELL FARMS COGDELL WEDDING CANCER SURVIVORS NATHAN M. STANFORDPictures of Nathan
PHOTO ALBUMSCogdell Family Photos Shirley Cogdell Children Cogdell Farms Cogdell Deerstand John Henry Cogdell
Privacy PolicyAt Cogdell Insurance Agency, our privacy policy is clear:We collect no information about you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide that information to us.You do not have to give us personal information to visit our website.  If you choose to provide us with additional information about yourself thru an email message, form, survey, etc., we will only maintain the information as long as needed to respond to your question or to fulfill the stated purpose of the communication.Cogdell Insurance Agency does not disclose, give, sell or transfer any personal information about our visitors or personally provided information, unless required by law enforcement or statute.(Note: For more information on the Medical Policy Rule, please go to www.hhs.gov/ocr/hipaa.)Site SecurityFor site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users. we may employ software programs to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.  In the event of authorized law enforcement investigations, and pursuant to any required legal process, information from these sources may be used to help identify an individual.Copyright 2018 Cogdell Insurance Agency. All rights reserved.Web Hosting by Yahoo111 North Main StreetLexington, TN 38351ph: 731-968-4300fax: 731-968-4001bobbycogdell@charter.net
